==========================================================================================
QUERY: how do I verify a webhook signature
  [vector]
    dist=0.318  # Webhooks  Webhooks let Cobalt Loop notify your own server when a workflow event happens,
    dist=0.364  Subject: Webhook signature verification always fails  Description: I'm computing HMAC-SHA2
    dist=0.534  Subject: Webhook marked Failed after exactly 4 retries, is that expected?  Description: Ou
  [keyword]
    rank=0.076  # Webhooks  Webhooks let Cobalt Loop notify your own server when a workflow event happens,
  [hybrid]
    score=0.0328  # Webhooks  Webhooks let Cobalt Loop notify your own server when a workflow event happens,
    score=0.0161  Subject: Webhook signature verification always fails  Description: I'm computing HMAC-SHA2
    score=0.0159  Subject: Webhook marked Failed after exactly 4 retries, is that expected?  Description: Ou
==========================================================================================
QUERY: what happens if I exceed my rate limit
  [vector]
    dist=0.538  # Billing & Plans  ## Plan comparison  | Feature | Free | Pro | Business | Enterprise | |-
    dist=0.558  # Rate Limits  Cobalt Loop enforces rate limits per API key to keep the platform stable fo
    dist=0.631  Subject: Monthly task limit exceeded ù will our workflows stop running?  Description: We j
  [keyword]
    rank=0.089  # Rate Limits  Cobalt Loop enforces rate limits per API key to keep the platform stable fo
    rank=0.076  # Troubleshooting Common Errors  ## Workflow runs but the action doesn't happen  Most comm
    rank=0.051  # Authentication & API Keys  All requests to the Cobalt Loop REST API must include a valid
  [hybrid]
    score=0.0325  # Rate Limits  Cobalt Loop enforces rate limits per API key to keep the platform stable fo
    score=0.0164  # Billing & Plans  ## Plan comparison  | Feature | Free | Pro | Business | Enterprise | |-
    score=0.0161  # Troubleshooting Common Errors  ## Workflow runs but the action doesn't happen  Most comm
==========================================================================================
QUERY: how do I connect Slack to my account
  [vector]
    dist=0.402  Subject: Slack action failing with channel_not_found  Description: Our Send Message action
